Hello, this is Sakura Endo.
Well, this is Saxampo No. 4.
I'm here in Okinawa.
And for this fourth installment...
I've brought someone I like a little bit.
Hello.
Hey there!
I'm Ten Yamazaki from Sakurazaka Hot Sex.
This is Ten-chan.
Hello, hello.
It's so bright!
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm glad you're here. I saw you yesterday.
Really? Yeah, I'm sure.
I'm glad. I didn't think I'd get a shot with you.
Oh, really? Yeah, I'm glad.
I'm glad it came true.
Yay! Yay!
Yesterday's walk was easy.
Okay. - Okay. Let's go easy then.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going
I'm off! I'm off!
We're good friends... we're good friends... we're good friends... we're good friends... we're good friends... we're good friends... we're good friends... we're good friends... we're good friends...
He saw us at the concert and delivered a message saying how much he liked your performance and how cool it was.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The staff, you know... the staff started talking to him.
I'm so glad. We even went out for dinner.
We went out for dinner, got a brochure... and came to Koi no Shima, the island of love.
There's a place called Umikaji Terrace. There's lots of food here.
We haven't eaten yet. We're starving. We haven't eaten yet today. That's right. We're starving.
What do you want to eat?
What do you think?
But don't they have hamburgers or something famous?
There are a lot of burgers here.
I think they're famous for tacos, too.
I know what you mean.
I wonder what it is? But what's it famous for?
Isn't everything famous?
I guess so.
It's random.
But everything looks delicious, really.
Are those tacos?
Sure. You want to go upstairs?
Let's go upstairs.
There are so many places to eat, it's hard to choose!
It's 49 steps.
We're the same.
I can't decide for the rest of my life.
Wow, that looks good!
It's a burger place.
And it looks like you're gonna sit down.
Sure.
This is the place.
You want to come in?
Let's go in.
Surprisingly quick.
One avocado steak and one...
And one mozzarella steak, please.
Yes, ma'am. Yes, sir.
Cute.
Looks delicious.
Look at this. Isn't this amazing?
Oh, my God.
Looks so good.
Cheers.
Mm-hmm.
Yum.
Yay. - Yay.
Yay.
Yummy.
Bon appétit!
Mmm.
Oh!
Have you ever had a good taco?
No, it's my first time.
You don't want me to report back? I don't mind if you do.
It's good. It's so good.
It's really nice. It's like we just walk around and eat.
Great! Great taki walk!
Third time in Okinawa? Third time?
Third time this year. That's great.Third time this year. It's amazing, isn't it?
It's a joint. He's been back more than 10 times.
That's true, isn't it?
Swart, filming...
You got to shoot, but I didn't get to do much sightseeing.
This is the first time I've been able to relax.
Is this a tailwind?
It's easier to eat here.
You want to move?
Oh, that's good.
It's a little easier to eat.
It's easier to eat.
It's good.
Lickety-split.
They have a funny face. It's a funny face.
He comes over here sometimes.
I'm eating fries with a face like this.
It's frustrating. It's frustrating. It's frustrating.
That was good. Hey, I'm full.
I'm full. I'm full. I'm full.
There it is. There it is.
There it is! There it is!
There it is! There it is! There it is! There's a cart full of them, fast, fast!
Wow, amazing.
Ta-da!
What is this place?
This is interesting. Wow, this is great.
Let's go in. But Emma said she's coming from here.
Let's go in. Let's go in. Want to come in? Let's go in.
You know, I wonder where we're gonna get this.
I'm gonna have to get Emma.
Hey.
They're selling them at number one on the map.
Oh, yeah, it's at the very end.
Just a little...
Just take a picture.
Let's make it happen.
I sat down just in case...
I just sat down.
I'm just trying to sit down.
I'm just saying there's this kind of thing.
Yes, there are. It's an island of love.
If you're serious about love...
I'd recommend it.
I have to draw Emma.
What should we draw?
Let's draw her in AR. In AR.
Let's make him love Saku-chan.
Let's make him love Nen-chan.
Yay!
What the heck is this?
But we're getting to the point.
Yeah, they're all gone. Let's go to the next one, shall we?
I just want to go in the ocean.
We just can't help it.
We're moving on.
Yay!
This is Suboya. This is Suboya.
We're here on Yachibun Street.
Yes, it seems to be a shopping street. I'm very happy.
I heard there's a lot of Okinawan style shops here.
I hear there's a lot of Okinawan things here.
Let's go there. Let's go there.
I heard there are many Okinawan things.
I want to see the early days.
I love the early days, too.
It's nice, isn't it?
It's very Okinawan.
Okinawan.
See?
I'm not very good at this.
Let's hit it.
We have a change of players.
What's so cute here?
It's so cute!
So cute!
They come as a set of two.
What?
I want one.
I want a shisa.
They're so cute.
Their faces are totally different.
I think you have a different face.
One by one.
We could buy one of these and split it in half.
One side each.One side at a time.
I'm sure.
Oh, it's true.
That's good.
Why don't we do that?
Let's do it.
Which one do you like?
I don't know which one I like.
It's cute. I'm torn.
I don't know. I don't know which one I like.
Can I pick a mission? Is she good?
Yeah, she's good.
You like this one or this one?
You want something different?
No, I like this one.
Okay, this one?
Yeah. - Okay.
Okay.
He's cute.
I've decided.
Our seesaw.
Oh, my goodness. Ours.
I can't wait to collect them.
There's no end to this.
Yeah, they're all so cute.
They're all so cute.
I like the sleeping one.
I like that he's sleeping.
It's cute. Isn't it cute from above? Sleeping.Cute. Isn't he cute from above? Sleeping.
I'll buy them both.
Oh, yeah?
I'll buy both of them. They're sleeping.
That's a good idea. That's a good idea.
Let's mix it up.
Thank you very much.
I went shopping.
I got a shisa.
Wow, that looks delicious!
What's with the bubbles?
Latte enjoys her tea while laughing at the white foam on her nose.
You put it on your nose?
Looks like fun!
Let's see.
Today.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Thank you
Pencon.
I don't have any Pong.
Excuse me.
Here you go.
I made a mistake.
Yeah, I made a mistake.
I did it.
That hurts.
That's so cute.
I did it.I did it.
I did it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Yes, sir. One moment, please.
That's our manager.
Thank you.
Buk Buk tea.
Two, please.
He's kind of Okinawan.
What's he like?
The manager.
Manager.
He must be from Okinawa.
I'm sure of it.
Yes, I'm sure.
Nankolunaisa.
Sakira
Aichi.
Oh, Kansai dialect?
What do you think?
Not Kansai dialect?
Yes, I know Aichi.
It's really standard Japanese now.
Oh, I see.
Oh.
I'm a mamma.
You don't have a dialect, do you?
Eh...
I'll teach you Kansai dialect then.
Oh, that's right, right, manager?Oh, yeah, right, manager.
Really?
Oh, that's nice.
Yeah, no.
Yeah. - Yeah.
That's, uh-uh.
Oh, that's nice.
It's so good.
Really? - Really?
Really?
That's not true.
I'm so happy.
Oh, you're good.
You're kidding?
Yeah, you're so good.
Thank you. Thank you.
That feels good. That feels good.
That feels good.
I don't know.
Oh, so that's what it feels like.
The way we drink it...Here is how to drink it
Hold the cup with both hands
Put your mouth to your mouth and drink the bubbles and tea
Please drink it together.
If it ends up on the flower
Please enjoy it while drinking.
Yes!
Ta-da!
Wow!
Amazing!
Bon appétit. Hold it with both hands.
Thank you. It's so cold.
Is this really how you drink it?
It's kind of squishy
I wonder if I'm doing it right.
I'll try it.
I'm sure you'll put it on.
Wait a minute.
It's not on yet.
I'm sure it's on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This one looks good.
It's like it's on and then it's off.
Yeah, I know.
I don't have any.
I know it's on.
If you look closely, you can see it.
That's funny.
Yeah, it's funny.
Let's film the scene. Let's shoot a scene.
Oh, he's so cute.
This is so good.
So cute.
It's so cute.
Hmm?
Oh, my God.
What's wrong?
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Wrong volume.
Wrong volume. Wrong volume.
It was a little too good to be true.
It was pretty loud, wasn't it?
Did I make a mistake?
It's okay. It's okay.
It was wrong volume.
And then it was like this.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
It's like a town!
There's a really big Mr. C!
That big C!
In the photo album.
Oh, did you open it?
I think I just passed it.
Oh, no?
Oh, my God.
That looks familiar.
Really?
From a distance.From a distance
Here it is.
I hope you like it.
All of you!
A pilgrimage to a holy place.
I found Mr. Saundergear.
I'm going there.
I heard they serve freshly fried food.
I want to eat it for sure!
Hello.
What?
They sell all sizes!
So cute! It's like an egg.
One S. Original.
Yes, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Ta-da!
After you.
You don't mind?
Yeah, go ahead, eat.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
Hot!
Hot?
Yes, it is.
It smells so good.
Yum! Is it good?
Yum!
It's so hot!It's so hot!
No way!
It's delicious!
Thank you. Thank you.
Bon appétit.
It's hot.
Freshly fried. Delicious.
It's so hot.
It's so good.
Well, as soon as I finish this, I'm heading back to the hotel.
Let's go, let's go, let's go. Bye-bye.
We're here. We're at the hotel.
We're at the hotel. Yay. The sun is setting.
The sun has set.
It's so spacious.
It's cool.
It's nice and cool.
Keung.
Ta-da!
It's so beautiful. It's the ocean.
It looks like a castle.
Wait, Mitsutsuki, there's something here.
What's this?
God, this is our pool! Our pool! The one we've been looking forward to!
This is awesome!
Great, great, great, great, great!
Good morning.
Good morning. Good morning. We're in the same room.
Same room.
We've never been in the same room on an expedition.I don't think we'll be sharing a room on an expedition.
So it's just you and me. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm opening the door. This way.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Gasp!
Excuse me, sir. Thank you for the drink.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What? What? What's this?
What is it? What? What? What?
What? What is this?
What? What is it?
What's with the gen...
What? Rock-paper-scissors?
What? What?
Look.
What?
Rock, paper, scissors?
Huh?
What? Where are you looking?
Look, there's a bear.
What? Huh?
Huh? I don't know what to do.
What?
Wait a minute. That's great.
Oh, my gosh, my gosh, my gosh.
Ta-da!
What's this place?
It's huge!
It's great! That's great.
Two beds.
Hey.
Oh, this one here...
Isn't that a pool?
Pool.
Wow.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Can you see it?
It's so beautiful!
This is the ocean.
The ocean's nice. They're playing. They're playing in the sand.
Wow, you're so transparent. I'm so embarrassed.
Oh, I'm so embarrassed.
I'm so embarrassed. I'm so transparent.
This is the shower. The shower.
It's big.
Bath.
Wow, yay!
I'm going to go to the pool now.
I'm off!
Bye, bye.
I'm dressed now.
I'm looking forward to it.
It's my first time in a night pool.
Hey, it's true.
I can't wait to go to the pool at this time of night.What fun to have a pool at this time of the day!
Oh, my God.
That's great.
I just want to go. Come on.
What's so great about it?
It's great.
Have a good day.
Oh, wait, it's warm.
It's warm.
No way.
Oh, it's warm in there.
Feels good.
I want to go that way.
What is this place?
What is this place? What is this place?
That feels good.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
That's good. That's good.
That feels good.
Feels good.
No, no, no, no, no.
I think I'm gonna go play a little harder now.
Let's put the camera down.Let's put the camera down.
Bye-bye, guys.
Bye-bye.
It's just us now.
We're playing... a lot.
This is great.
I like this kind of thing.
Aren't the stars so beautiful?
That's what I'm talking about.
I love the way it looks!
Oh, wow.
Can't you see it?
It's so beautiful.
I love it.
I like it. - I like it.
That's nice.
Feels good.
It smells so good.
I love my smell.
It's nice, isn't it?
I love it so much.
You're so cute.
It's all over your face.
It's gone.
It's fun.
I think we've got about 10 minutes left.I think we've got about 10 minutes left.
Hey, how much more?
I'm going to swim like crazy.
See you later.
Bye bye.
Here's our hotel room.
This is our room.
This is our bed room.
I was going to eat a candy bar.
It's been a long day.
It was so much fun.
I had so much fun.
That was great.
Hey.
You have any problems?
Do you have any problems?
Worries?
No.
That's good.
Yes?
No.
But lately...
I don't have a dream for the future.
I don't have a dream that I want to do in the future.
Well, no. It's the same.
No?
I've already thought about it.
No, I think so.
I think.Hey.
If you were already active...
Well, you've graduated.
I'm worried about you.
I'm sorry.
She's Asuka's child, right?
I wonder...
Yes.
Even now?
I hope so.
Don't you?
Yes, I do.
I'm sure it is.
And I was telling Asuka...
What?
That you and Asuka are good friends.
Yes, yes.
You told her?
I told her.
Mm-hm.
You know, the other day...
He said hello to you.
What?
The first time we met.
He told me.
Asuka told you?
When did she tell you that?
When we met at TCC?
He said he'd be nice to me.
And then...So...
Tell him it's his mother, too.
Did you tell her?
I don't know.
She said "mom.
But she really is my mom.
Oh, really?
Yeah, really.
A mother.
Yeah. - Yeah.
I kind of felt like a big brother.
Mm-hm.
Yeah, something like that.
It's okay.
It's like a mother.
It's nice to have someone like that in the group.
Isn't it great to be in a group?
It's great, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
It's so great.
It's so good.
I never thought we'd be this close.
Yeah. - Yeah.
You're not in the group anymore.
Not anymore.
I mean, not just Asuka.
It's true.
First-term students.
Nogizaka
You've changed so much.You've changed so much, haven't you?
That's what I've been trying to make.
One of the first students is no longer with us.
That's right.
But Sakura, too...
Yeah.
Another first-term student.
No, thank you.
Right?
Yeah.
More and more now.
Oh, yeah, and now you.
Yeah.
You're graduating.
More and more and more and more and more.
What do you think? How are you feeling?
I don't know.
But...
I wonder... if the seniors I admired so much...
Quitting...
It's so strange.
Yeah.
But... But it's something...
I don't know...
I don't know... maybe I don't really feel it, to be honest.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Even if you quit, I'll still see you.Even if you quit, I'll still see you.
Oh...
I mean...
Yeah.
And it's sad to see her go.
That's true.
I'm a first generation student.
Ha-ha-ha.
I really am.
You're right.
Okay, you're gonna have to tell me the big story at 18.
Oh, no.
But not too much.
Yeah, not really.
I don't know.
I don't know if this is gonna sound bad, but I feel like I might not be as responsible.
In a way, I don't feel pressure.
But that's good... because I think you're the type of person who can't handle pressure.
Even after I realized that, I tried not to think about it too much.
I tried not to think too much about it.
I can't do anything if I think I have to pull myself up by the bootstraps or carry the load.
I can't do anything if I think about it too much.
I think I'm better suited to being natural.
What do you think? How about you, Sakira? I still have Sankisei.
Well, since you're here...
I'm still following him too.
But you know what?
But you were so cool.
It said "Gokisei" instead of "Sankisei." That was really cool.
It really says that we are Nogizaka46. We are Nogizaka46.
We are Nogizaka46.
I'm sure the fans understand. I think they can sense it.
But when I see you working so hard, it makes me want to do my best.
Really? Really?
I feel like I'm doing my best.
I'm like, "I gotta work harder." No, you're right, I should work harder too.
But you're a good inspiration.
Yeah, it's really stimulating.
But everything's best when you're having fun, right?
That's right.
It's refreshing, isn't it?
Right?
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm going to bed!
Let's go to bed.
Okay, come a little closer.
That was delicious.
Hey, it was good.
It was, actually.
Yeah, actually.
This is where it ends.
Oh, yeah.
This is where the book ends.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Well, thank you very much.
It's a pleasure.
First guest
first guest First guest
Thank you.
Okay, so the second half.
Yeah.
Sakura Zaka Channel.
Yes, sir.
On Ten Tabi.
Yes.
Please come.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'm glad you're coming.
Let's have fun.
I'm glad.
I'll enjoy it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's have fun
Let's have fun.
Okay.
Bye.
Good night.
Bye-bye.
Good night.Good night.
Good night.
Bye-bye.
Next preview
Here you go.
I see.
You sure?
Yes, it's okay.
Downstairs!
There you go.
Whoa!
Done!
He's so cute.
Well, good night, everybody.
Good night.
I don't know what we're gonna do.I don't know what we're gonna do.
What do we do?
Shall I show you what I've brought?
Let me show you what I brought.
Here's my belt.
Oh! Here it is.
A belt!
I'll put ice cream on it.
Okay, bye.
Bye, bye, bye.
Good night.
Thank you for watching.